和单方面审查的可接受性有关
That has to do with the admissibility of ex parte examinations?
那是一个最高法院的案子  不是吗
That was a-a Supreme Court case, wasn't it?
没错  怎么说的来着
That's right. How did it go?
"唯一能够满足
"The only indicium of reliability
"宪法要求的可靠性标准
sufficient to satisfy constitutional demands
"就是宪法本身规定的
is the one the Constitution actually prescribes --
"对质条款"
confrontation."
经典的斯卡利亚式判决
It's classic Scalia.
我不禁想到受害者
I can't help but think about victims
被迫在公开法庭上和袭击者对质
forced to confront ‭their assailants in open court
但另一方面
but on the other hand
第六修正案相当有力
the Sixth Amendment is pretty controlling.
对不起
I'm sorry.
看我  都开始讨论宪法问题了
I just -- I get rolling on constitutional questions.